{
    "subject": "resource/Enemy_(American_band)",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "The hometown of Enemy (American band) is United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9385696649551392,
            "question": "Is Enemy a band from the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8628606796264648,
            "question": "What is the hometown of Enemy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8501313328742981,
            "question": "Where is Enemy (American band) from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7944623231887817,
            "question": "Is Enemy based in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.703644871711731,
            "question": "In which country is Enemy's hometown located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6333848834037781,
            "question": "What is the nationality of Enemy (American band)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34326595067977905,
            "question": "Where did Enemy originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22897957265377045,
            "question": "What is Enemy's place of origin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19246701896190643,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the origins of Enemy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1784016340970993,
            "question": "What country considers Enemy as one of its own musical groups?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The hometown of Enemy (American band) is United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8819_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about the origins of Enemy?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8819_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Enemy's place of origin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8819_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Enemy originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8819_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8819_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response to your query:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that The Enemy is a British rock band, not an American band. According to the documents, their hometown is Coventry, which is located in England. There is no mention of them being from the United States."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about the rock band The Enemy and their performances, albums, and history but do not mention anything about the band's hometown or its location. Therefore, based on the given context, it cannot be confirmed that the hometown of The Enemy is in the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The Enemy mentioned in the context information is a British rock band, not an American one.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The text states The Enemy are an English rock band formed in 2006.",
            "category": 4
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of an American band called \"Enemy\" in the provided context information, which exclusively discusses a British rock band also named \"The Enemy\".",
            "category": 4
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information states that The Enemy (English band) formed in Coventry, UK, and their hometown is mentioned as Coventry. There is no information suggesting an American connection or a United States hometown for the band.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}